AAKANKSHA SEHRAWAT

Choreographer | Teacher | Entrepreneur Performing Artist | Counselor

PROFILE

A budding entrepreneur and a renowned choreographer and artist specialising in dance styles like Kathak, Afro, Dancehall, Semi-Classical and Hip Hop. Has worked with names like Shoojit Sircar, Kanika Kapoor, Salman Yusuf Khan, Raftaar and brands like T-series, Zee Music, Ford Motors, Cvent, HnM, Noise, frogalised productions etc. Trained in Mumbai, Dubai and London, currently taking up freelance projects and running an animal welfare NGO taking care of a number of strays in the city.

SKILLS

- Direction and choreography
- Event Management
- Emotional Intelligence
- · Confidence and humor
- · Creative thinking
- English Proficiency
- Social Media Marketing
- MS Office

CONTACT



+91 8076529557



ywcaakanksha@gmail.com



www.dancewithaakanksha.com



DLF Cyber City, Gurgaon

EDUCATION

Tagore International, New Delhi (2014)CBSE

• CGPA: 9.6

• Aggregate: 97.8%

Lady Shri Ram College for Women (2017)

Delhi University

• BA Psychology Hons.

NMIMS, Mumbai (2020)

• Diploma in Human Resource Management

Shri Ram Bhartiya Kala Kendra

• Kathak: Lucknow Gharana

WORK EXPERIENCE

TGT

The Shri Ram School (2018 - 2019)

Directing annual productions; managing performing arts IT department; designing dance curriculum for each form exclusively; implementing the same during classes and preparing detailed reports every semester

Guest Faculty

Ambience Public School : Urban Dance Teacher Blue Bells School - Dance Camp Facilitator Sun Sea Public School - Choreographer

Performing Artist/Choreographer

Indian Council for Cultural Relations (2017 - 2021)

Represented India at festivals and events in various cities across countries like Fiji, Tuvalu and Mexico.

Projects and Internships: Counselor

National Social Service (2015 - 2017) Rajiv Gandhi Mahila Vikas Pariyojna (2016) Cognizavest, Organisational Psychology (2021)

AWARDS AND FELICITATIONS

- Fiji High Commission
- Indian Embassy in Mexico
- IIT Delhi Rendezvous
- TSRS Teachers Awards
- World Afro Championship, Dubai